const FisData = [
    {
      question: "What is a financial intermediary service?",
      answer:
        "Accordion components are user interface elements used for organizing and presenting content in a collapsible manner. They typically consist of a header, content, and an expand/collapse action."
    },
    {
      question: "Is Moshav Capital's financial intermediary service regulated?",
      answer:
        "They are commonly employed in various contexts, including FAQs, product descriptions, navigation menus, settings panels, and data tables, to save screen space and provide a structured and user-friendly interface for presenting information or options."
    },
    {
      question: "How does Moshav Capital's FIS benefit agribusinesses?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    }
  ];


  const IaasData = [
    {
      question: "What is Infrastructure-As-A-Service (IAAS)?",
      answer:
        "Accordion components are user interface elements used for organizing and presenting content in a collapsible manner. They typically consist of a header, content, and an expand/collapse action."
    },
    {
      question: "How does Moshav Capital's IAAS benefit agribusinesses?",
      answer:
        "They are commonly employed in various contexts, including FAQs, product descriptions, navigation menus, settings panels, and data tables, to save screen space and provide a structured and user-friendly interface for presenting information or options."
    },
    {
      question: "Can I access Moshav Capital's IAAS from anywhere?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    }
  ];

  const CommodityData = [
    {
      question: "How does Moshav Capital's commodity warehousing benefit agribusinesses?",
      answer:
        "Accordion components are user interface elements used for organizing and presenting content in a collapsible manner. They typically consist of a header, content, and an expand/collapse action."
    },
    {
      question: "What is collateral management in agribusiness?",
      answer:
        "They are commonly employed in various contexts, including FAQs, product descriptions, navigation menus, settings panels, and data tables, to save screen space and provide a structured and user-friendly interface for presenting information or options."
    },
    {
      question: "How does Moshav Capital ensure transparency in collateral management?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    }
  ];

  const ClusterData = [
    {
      question: "What is a brokerage service in agribusiness?",
      answer:
        "Accordion components are user interface elements used for organizing and presenting content in a collapsible manner. They typically consist of a header, content, and an expand/collapse action."
    },
    {
      question: "How does Moshav Capital's brokerage service work?",
      answer:
        "They are commonly employed in various contexts, including FAQs, product descriptions, navigation menus, settings panels, and data tables, to save screen space and provide a structured and user-friendly interface for presenting information or options."
    },
    {
      question: "What types of activities are included in cluster marketing support?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    }
  ];
  
  const HomeData = [
    {
      question: "What services does Moshav Capital provide to agribusiness enterprises?",
      answer:
        "Accordion components are user interface elements used for organizing and presenting content in a collapsible manner. They typically consist of a header, content, and an expand/collapse action."
    },
    {
      question: "How can Moshav Capital's financial solutions benefit my agribusiness?",
      answer:
        "They are commonly employed in various contexts, including FAQs, product descriptions, navigation menus, settings panels, and data tables, to save screen space and provide a structured and user-friendly interface for presenting information or options."
    },
    {
      question: "What is commodity warehousing and how does it help agribusinesses?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    },
    {
      question: "How does Moshav Capital support cluster marketing for agribusinesses?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    },
    {
      question: "Is Moshav Capital's infrastructure-as-a-service beneficial for agribusiness?",
      answer:
        "The accordion is a musical instrument with a keyboard and bellows. It produces sound by air passing over reeds when the player expands or compresses the bellows, used in various music genres."
    }
  ];


  const AboutData = [
    {
      icon: `<svg  width="50" height="50" viewBox="0 0 150 150" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_318_8308)">
      <path d="M56.25 87.5C56.25 97.8562 73.0375 106.25 93.75 106.25C114.462 106.25 131.25 97.8562 131.25 87.5C131.25 77.1438 114.462 68.75 93.75 68.75C73.0375 68.75 56.25 77.1438 56.25 87.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M56.25 87.5V112.5C56.25 122.85 73.0375 131.25 93.75 131.25C114.462 131.25 131.25 122.85 131.25 112.5V87.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M18.75 37.5C18.75 44.2 25.9 50.3875 37.5 53.7375C49.1 57.0875 63.4 57.0875 75 53.7375C86.6 50.3875 93.75 44.2 93.75 37.5C93.75 30.8 86.6 24.6125 75 21.2625C63.4 17.9125 49.1 17.9125 37.5 21.2625C25.9 24.6125 18.75 30.8 18.75 37.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M18.75 37.5V100C18.75 105.55 23.575 109.062 31.25 112.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M18.75 68.75C18.75 74.3 23.575 77.8125 31.25 81.25" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_318_8308">
      <rect width="150" height="150" fill="white"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>`,
      question: "Tailored Financial Solutions",
      listOne: "Access tailored credit facilities and financing options designed specifically for agribusinesses, addressing diverse needs and business goals.",
      listTwo: "Benefit from expert collateral management solutions to optimize asset utilization and secure financing for growth and expansion.",
      listThree: "Partner with leading insurance providers through Moshav Capital to obtain tailored micro insurance products covering crop, livestock, and equipment risks.",
      listfour: "Moshav Capital's services are uniquely crafted to address the specific challenges and goals of agribusinesses, providing personalized support for sustainable growth and success."
    },
    {
      icon: ` <svg width="50" height="50" viewBox="0 0 150 150" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_318_8319)">
      <path d="M25 87.5V68.75C25 55.4892 30.2678 42.7715 39.6447 33.3947C49.0215 24.0178 61.7392 18.75 75 18.75C88.2608 18.75 100.979 24.0178 110.355 33.3947C119.732 42.7715 125 55.4892 125 68.75V87.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M112.5 118.75C112.5 129.106 95.7125 137.5 75 137.5" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M25 87.5C25 84.1848 26.317 81.0054 28.6612 78.6612C31.0054 76.317 34.1848 75 37.5 75H43.75C47.0652 75 50.2446 76.317 52.5888 78.6612C54.933 81.0054 56.25 84.1848 56.25 87.5V106.25C56.25 109.565 54.933 112.745 52.5888 115.089C50.2446 117.433 47.0652 118.75 43.75 118.75H37.5C34.1848 118.75 31.0054 117.433 28.6612 115.089C26.317 112.745 25 109.565 25 106.25V87.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M93.75 87.5C93.75 84.1848 95.067 81.0054 97.4112 78.6612C99.7554 76.317 102.935 75 106.25 75H112.5C115.815 75 118.995 76.317 121.339 78.6612C123.683 81.0054 125 84.1848 125 87.5V106.25C125 109.565 123.683 112.745 121.339 115.089C118.995 117.433 115.815 118.75 112.5 118.75H106.25C102.935 118.75 99.7554 117.433 97.4112 115.089C95.067 112.745 93.75 109.565 93.75 106.25V87.5Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_318_8319">
      <rect width="150" height="150" fill="white"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>`,
      question: "Comprehensive support ecosystem",
      listOne: "Moshav Capital fosters collaborative marketing efforts among agribusinesses, facilitating partnerships and initiatives to access new markets and enhance visibility.",
      listTwo: "Access expert brokerage services through Moshav Capital to streamline trade and market access, ensuring efficient transactions and optimized distribution.",
      listThree: "Leverage Moshav Capital's IaaS solutions to optimize operations and reduce costs, benefiting from technology and infrastructure support tailored for agribusiness growth.",
      listfour: ""
    },
    {
      icon: `<svg width="40" height="40" viewBox="0 0 40 40" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_489_2330)">
      <path d="M10 15C10 17.6522 11.0536 20.1957 12.9289 22.0711C14.8043 23.9464 17.3478 25 20 25C22.6522 25 25.1957 23.9464 27.0711 22.0711C28.9464 20.1957 30 17.6522 30 15C30 12.3478 28.9464 9.8043 27.0711 7.92893C25.1957 6.05357 22.6522 5 20 5C17.3478 5 14.8043 6.05357 12.9289 7.92893C11.0536 9.8043 10 12.3478 10 15Z" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M20 25L25.6667 34.8167L28.33 29.4283L34.3267 29.815L28.66 20" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M11.3385 20L5.67188 29.8167L11.6685 29.4283L14.3319 34.815L19.9985 25" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_489_2330">
      <rect width="40" height="40" fill="white"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>
      `,
      question: "Reliable and secure warehousing",
      listOne: "Moshav Capital operates secure storage facilities licensed by regulatory authorities, ensuring optimal conditions for various commodities.",
      listTwo: "Clients receive official warehouse receipts from Moshav Capital, which can be used as collateral for financing, providing additional liquidity and flexibility for business operations.",
      listThree: "",
      listfour: ""
    },
    {
      icon: `<svg width="50" height="50" viewBox="0 0 150 151" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg">
      <g clip-path="url(#clip0_318_8338)">
      <path d="M18.75 106.75L56.25 69.25L81.25 94.25L131.25 44.25" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      <path d="M87.5 44.25H131.25V88" stroke="#1E772C" stroke-width="4.16667" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"/>
      </g>
      <defs>
      <clipPath id="clip0_318_8338">
      <rect width="150" height="150" fill="white" transform="translate(0 0.5)"/>
      </clipPath>
      </defs>
      </svg>`,
      question: "Commitment to Innovation & Sustainability",
      listOne: "Moshav Capital is committed to delivering innovative solutions tailored for agribusinesses, ensuring long-term success through cutting-edge approaches and technologies.",
      listTwo: "We prioritize responsible resource management, promoting sustainable agricultural practices to minimize environmental impact and enhance long-term viability.",
      listThree: "Moshav Capital fosters knowledge sharing and collaborative partnerships within the agribusiness sector, creating synergies that drive sustainable growth and development.",
      listfour: ""
    },
  ]

  

const exportedData = {
    IaasData,
    ClusterData,
    FisData,
    CommodityData,
    HomeData,
    AboutData
}


export default exportedData;
  